rebeccaminkoff.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy & Security – Rebecca Minkoff

PRIVACY

All of our transactions are protected by powerful SSL encryption software and McAfee Secure. We guarantee that every transaction you make at RebeccaMinkoff.com will be 100% safe.

SECURITY

November 5, 2014

Introduction

This Privacy and Usage Policy applies to your use of the website located at www.rebeccaminkoff.com, www.uriminkoff.com, and any other online and mobile websites, blogs and mobile applications operated by Rebecca Minkoff LLC and its affiliates (collectively, for purposes of this Privacy and Usage Policy and Terms of Use “Rebecca Minkoff”) that are related to www.rebeccaminkoff.com and www.uriminkoff.com (collectively, the “website”). This information is used to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions. Neither your name nor anything about you is sold to any other non-affiliated company or agency. However, as described in greater detail below, we may share your information under certain circumstances with business partners that help this site function or assist us in fulfilling your order. This Privacy and Usage Policy only covers information collected on the website, and does not cover any information collected offline by Rebecca Minkoff, including information collected at our partner department stores or freestanding stores.

This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use certain pieces of that information. The notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the personal information. We also tell you how you can reach us to ask us to (i) access, change or not use the personal information you have provided to us, (ii) withdraw any consent you previously provided to us, (iii) tell us to refrain from communicating with you about our products or services, and (iv) answer any questions you may have about our privacy practices. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our website. You can tell if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears on this policy.

Information We Collect and How We Use It

We sometimes ask you for certain kinds of personal information to provide the services you request. This information includes:

Shopping - Through this website, you will be able to purchase Rebecca Minkoff products and gift cards. We ask for information such as your name, billing and shipping address, telephone number, email address and payment card information in order to process your purchase, confirm your order and ship the items to you. If you elect to be added to the Rebecca Minkoff email list, we may use your contact information to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions.

My Account - You have the opportunity to create a personal shopping account with Rebecca Minkoff, which allows you to shop faster and easier. Using a user name and a password of your choice, you may access your account online at any time to add, delete, or change information. In creating this account, you authorize Rebecca Minkoff to store your name and email address. Should you elect to do so, you may also include in your “My Account” your telephone number, payment card information, and shipping and billing addresses. If you choose to include such additional information then you are also authorizing Rebecca Minkoff to store such information until such time you elect to change or delete it. Each of these options is for your convenience only. If you ever use a public computer to visit the “My Account” section of our website we strongly encourage you to log out at the conclusion of your session.

Through the “My Account” feature, you may create a Wish List of products you want and share the items on your list by copying and pasting the URL. You may elect to make this Wish List public, so that friends and family can search for you by either name or email address.

Email List - When you create an account with Rebecca Minkoff, you will be given the option to be added to the Rebecca Minkoff email list. Whether or not you select this option, your personal information will never be shared with or sold to anyone. Subscriptions to the email list can be cancelled at any time. To be removed from our email list, please email us at customercare@rebeccaminkoff.com and include your name and the address in the message, or click the unsubscribe button found at the bottom of the emails we send you.

Purchases - When you place an order, you will be asked to provide your credit card information.

Customer Service - If you call our Customer Service center, we may ask for information such as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number and if you choose to make a purchase, your credit card information. We use this information to assist you and to process your transaction. Purchases - When you place an order, you will be asked to provide your credit card information. Rebecca Minkoff does not store your credit card information unless you choose to include it in your “My Account” (see above).

Electronic Newsletters - You may be able to sign up on this site to receive electronic newsletters and promotional emails from Rebecca Minkoff. To sign up we may ask for information such as your name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, gender, age, and email preferences.

You will receive promotional emails from us only if you have asked to receive them. If you do not want to receive e-mail from Rebecca Minkoff you may click on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email communication sent by us. Please allow us ten (10) business days from when the request was received to complete the removal, as some of our promotions may already have been in process before you submitted your request.

Surveys, Sweepstakes and Promotions - On this website, you may be able to participate in surveys, sweepstakes and promotions. If you choose to participate in these promotions, we may request information such as your name, age, email address, mailing address, telephone number, and interests or product preferences. This information is used to enter you into our contests, sweepstakes and other promotions. By participating in our surveys, sweepstakes and promotions you give us consent to use this information to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions.

Email to a Friend - You may be able to share certain content from this website with your friends. In order to do so, we may ask for information such as your name, email address, zip code and telephone number. We will not include any other advertisements within the message sent your friends.

Other Site Features - We offer visitors to this website various features for their information and enjoyment, which we may change from time to time. We may ask you to submit certain personal information so we can provide you with these features and send you communications about our products, services and promotions.

As of November 16, 2016 customer ratings are subject to a overall rating standard.

RM Squad Terms and Conditions

The RM Squad Program (“RM Squad”) is an insider program offered by Rebecca Minkoff, LLC (“Rebecca Minkoff”) to its customers based in the United States. You must be thirteen years or older to participate in the RM Squad. Eligible minors must obtain their parent or legal guardian’s consent prior to participation.

To join the RM Squad you must submit the form on the hosted webpage and provide your name, address, phone number, and create a username and password. In addition, you will be asked for but not required to provide your date of birth (month and day). In able to be eligible for a Birthday Treat you must provide your date of birth.

If you’re in the RM Squad, you will receive special perks for being an RM insider, which may include rewards for your birthday (“Birthday Treat”), special sale invites, exclusive Rebecca insights, among other incentives.

RM Squad membership is limited to one per customer. Potential RM Squad points, discounts, and special offers are non-transferrable, non-assignable and may not be shared and are void where prohibited.

By submitting a form to join the RM Squad, you agree to receive advertising, marketing, and other communications from Rebecca Minkoff including the Rebecca Minkoff newsletter. If you do not wish to receive these communications you may opt-out by logging into your account and unsubscribing. Note that by unsubscribing from the Rebecca Minkoff newsletter you will also terminate your eligibility to earn perks through the RM Squad.

Rebecca Minkoff may, in its sole discretion, alter, limit, or modify the RM Squad Terms and Conditions, regulations, benefits, or eligibility to participate in the RM Squad. In addition, Rebecca Minkoff may discontinue the RM Squad at any time in tis sole discretion.

Rebecca Minkoff reserves the right to exclude customers from participating in the RM Squad in its sole discretion.

Information We Collect By Automated Means

Cookies

We work with service providers that use cookies to collect information about your visits to our website and other websites. This information is used to deliver targeted advertisements to you as you use the Internet. This information is anonymous and doesn’t personally identify you.

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about how you browse our website.

For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general Internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive.

Cookies help us to improve our website and to deliver a better and more customized service. They enable us:

To estimate usage numbers and patterns

To store information about your preferences, and to allow us to customize our website according to your individual interests.

To speed up your searches.

To recognize you when you return to our website.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the website or unable to avail of any of our services. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our website.

Pixel Tags

We also use "pixel tags" (sometimes called “Internet tags”, "web beacons" or "clear GIFS"), which are tiny graphic images, on our website. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers' online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our website and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.

Pixel tags on our website may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the site. This information may include your computer's Internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our site. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us.

We also work with business partners that use tracking technologies to deliver advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our advertising and other communications.

We may combine the information we collect through cookies and pixel tags with other information we have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our website, to personalize your online experience, to help us deliver information to you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

Use of Your Personal Information

We collect the information from our customers for various purposes, including:

Process transactions upon their request  
Improve our stores, website, customers shopping experience and quality of service  
Send communications about our products, services and promotions  
Prevent and detect fraud and abuse  
Process information or claims in connection with incidents at our stores  
Enable our service providers to perform certain activities on our behalf  
Comply with our legal obligations, policies and procedures and for internal administrative and analytics purposes.

Others with Whom We May Share Your Information

Service Providers: We also may disclose information to outside companies that help us bring you the products and services we offer. For example, we may work with an outside company to: (a) manage a database of customer information; (b) assist us in distributing e-mails; (c) assist us with direct marketing and data collection; (d) provide us data storage and analysis; (e) provide fraud prevention; (f) provide customer service by phone and (g) other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. We require that these outside companies agree to keep confidential all information we share with them and to use the information only to perform their obligations in the agreements.

If you use a social media platform (such as Facebook) or a mobile device or application to interact with the Website, there may be a specific privacy statement and/or policy that governs the use of Personal Data related to that platform or application. For example, if you use a mobile application and your mobile device’s settings allow it, Other may collect mobile location information from your device, whether or not you are logged into our Website. If you have questions about the security and privacy settings of your mobile device please refer to instructions from your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device, and for any third-party platform you use to access our Website, please review their privacy policies and terms of use.

Compliance with Law: We may provide access to information when legally required to do so, to cooperate with legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors of this website or the public.

Links to other sites

While visiting our website, you may link to sites operated by our business partners or other third parties. This does not mean that we endorse these sites. We do not make any representations or warranties about any website you may access through the Rebecca Minkoff website. They are independent from us, and we have no control over, or responsibility for, their information or activities.

In addition, our privacy practices may differ from those of these other sites. If you provide personal information at one of those sites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that site, not the Rebecca Minkoff Privacy and Usage Policy. Please make sure you understand the other site's privacy policy before providing personal information.

User Content

Rebecca Minkoff doesn't claim any ownership in any content that you upload on the Website, through a mobile application, blog or via any form of social media channel (including by submitting an image to your social media using the hashtags #MyRM, #MyUM, #rebeccaminkoff, #uriminkoff, #RMwatches, #RMFestival or @rebeccaminkoff) ("User Content"). After posting User Content, you retain the ownership right to all content, but you hereby grant to Rebecca Minkoff an irrevocable, fully-paid, worldwide, non-exclusive limited license to modify, publicly perform, display, reproduce, distribute, transmit, and copy the User Content on the Website, Rebecca Minkoff app, mobile website, email, and all applicable social channels, including but not limited to Facebook, Twitter, and Instagram.

Accordingly, you represent and warrant that you own all rights to the User Content that you upload to the Website, and it doesn't infringe on any other intellectual property rights, privacy rights, or publicity rights.

Rebecca Minkoff reserves the right to remove any User Content from the Website for any reason without prior notice.

Security

Rebecca Minkoff goes to great lengths to keep your financial information private and safe. We take appropriate physical, electronic and administrative steps to maintain the security and accuracy of personally identifiable information we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as employing electronic security systems and password protections that guard against unauthorized access. In addition, it is our policy to never send your credit card number via e-mail. Our customer service center and stores also operate over a private, secure network. Please note, however, that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

We use Secure Socket Layers (SSL), the industry standard in transferring information to process your orders. The SSL encrypts, or translates, your order information into a highly indecipherable code, which is processed immediately. All credit card transactions occur in a secure area of our site, to protect you from any loss, misuse or alteration of information collected. When you have finished shopping and begin the checkout process, you will move into the secure area of our site. Once you've entered, the page address (URL) will change from http to https, to let you know you are in a secure area. Also, a key or a closed lock will appear in the lower right hand corner of your screen to notify you of this change. You will remain in this secure zone for the entire checkout process.

Unfortunately, despite our best efforts, the transmission of data over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure. While we will use every reasonable means to ensure the security of information you transmit to us, we cannot guarantee that such information will not be intercepted by third parties. We will, however, prosecute any unauthorized or fraudulent transactions to the fullest extent permitted by law.

“SPOOFING” AND “PHISHING”

A common Internet scam is known as “spoofing” or “phishing.” This occurs when you receive an email from what appears to be a legitimate source requesting personal information from you. Please be aware that Rebecca Minkoff will NEVER send you an email requesting you to verify credit card, bank information, or any other personal information. If you ever receive an email that appears to be from us requesting such information from you, DO NOT respond to it, and DO NOT click on any links appearing in the email. Instead, please forward the email to us at customercare@rebeccaminkoff.com, as we will investigate all instances of possible Internet fraud.

Children's Privacy

Our website is not meant for children, and we do not collect any personal information from children under the age of thirteen. We will remove from our files any personally identifiable information of anyone we discover to be under thirteen years old. Our online contests or sweepstakes are restricted to entrants who are at least 18 years old.

California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: Rebecca Minkoff LLC, 16 West 22nd Street, 7th Floor, New York, NY 10010, Attn: Customer Service or by email to customercare@rebeccaminkoff.com. Please allow 30 days for a response.

Your Consent

You acknowledge that this Privacy and Usage Policy is part of the Terms of Use and you agree that using our website signifies your assent to Rebecca Minkoff's Privacy and Usage Policy and related terms of use provided above, is subject to all applicable laws, and is undertaken at your own risk. Rebecca Minkoff reserves the right to change this Privacy and Usage Policy at any time, without advance notice. If we decide to change our Privacy and Usage Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it.

SAFE HARBOUR PRIVACY POLICY

Rebecca Minkoff’s practices regarding the collection, storage, transfer, use and other processing of personal information follow the Safe Harbour principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, access, security, data integrity, and enforcement.

Notice - Rebecca Minkoff will give you timely and appropriate notice describing what personal information we’re collecting, how we will use it, and types of third parties with whom we may share it with.

Choice - Rebecca Minkoff will give you choices about the ways we use and share your personal information, and we will respect the choices you make.

Onward Transfer - When disclosing information to a third party, Rebecca Minkoff applies the notice and choice principles and takes appropriate measures to protect your privacy and the personal information we transfer.

Access - Rebecca Minkoff provides ways for you to access your personal information, as required by law, so that you can correct inaccuracies.

Security - Rebecca Minkoff will take appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect personal information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

Data Integrity - Rebecca Minkoff takes reasonable steps to ensure that personal information the company collects is relevant for the purposes for which it is to be used and that the information is reliable for its intended use and is accurate, complete and current.

Enforcement - Rebecca Minkoff uses a self-assessment approach to assure compliance with this privacy policy and periodically verifies that the policy is accurate, comprehensive for the information intended to be covered, prominently displayed, completely implemented and accessible and in conformity with the Principles.

We encourage interested persons to raise any concerns using the contact information below and we will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles.

HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about your privacy or security on our website, please contact us at customercare@rebeccaminkoff.com.

TERMS OF USE

November 5, 2014

Please read the following terms and conditions (the “Terms of Use”) carefully before using the website (the “Website”). By accessing this Website, you agree to be bound by these Terms of Use. If you do not agree with these Terms of Use, you may not use the Website. We recommend that you keep a printed copy of these Terms of Use for future reference.

Intellectual Property Ownership and Use

Please be aware that as you visit and navigate this website your use of our site is subject to applicable laws governing ownership and use of intellectual property, including our trademarks and copyrights.

For International Website Users: The Rebeccaminkoff.com Website is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are accessing the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Website, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Conditions of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

Trademarks

You may not use any of the Rebecca Minkoff trademarks or trade dress without our prior written permission. Trademarks or trade dress include the Rebecca Minkoff name and logos, and other graphics, logos, page headers, button icons, scripts, and service names of Rebecca Minkoff's products, services, and programs. Any other trademarks that appear on our website are the property of their owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by us or our affiliates

Copyright

All text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, and data compilations appearing on the website, as well as the software used to create them, are owned by Rebecca Minkoff and are protected by U.S. and foreign copyright laws. You may electronically copy and/or print “hard copies” from the website solely for personal, non-commercial purposes related to placing an order or shopping on the website. Any other use of any content included on the website, including linking or framing to this website, are strictly prohibited unless you first obtain our prior written consent.

Non-Confidential Information

Except for information necessary to place an order, we do not want you to send to us any confidential or proprietary information through this website. Any information, materials, suggestions, ideas or comments sent to us will be considered non-confidential, and by submitting it, you are giving us the absolute right to use, modify, reproduce, transmit, display and distribute it for any purpose whatsoever, with no payment or other compensation to you. However, we will not use your name unless we are required by law to identify the source of the materials, information, suggestions, ideas or comments, or unless we first obtain your permission.

Errors and Inaccuracies

We always try to provide complete, accurate, up-to-date information on our website. Unfortunately, despite those efforts human or technological errors may occur. This site may contain typographical mistakes, inaccuracies, or omissions, some of which may relate to pricing and availability, and some information may not be complete or current. We reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions, including after an order has been submitted, and to change or update information at any time without prior notice.

Disclaimer of Liability

We make no representations or warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, with respect to this website, its content, or the information available on or through it; they are provided "as is," with all faults. Except as otherwise provided under applicable laws, we will not be liable for any damages whatsoever arising out of or related to the use of this website or any other site linked to it. This limitation of liability applies to direct, indirect, consequential, special, punitive or other damages you or others may suffer, as well as damages for lost profits, business interruption or the loss of data or information, even if we are notified in advance of the potential for any such damages.

Applicable Law

By visiting the website, you agree that any dispute related to any transaction made on the website or any breach of these terms, you will first try in good faith to settle the dispute by sending a notice to the following address: Rebecca Minkoff, LLC, 16 West 22nd Street, 7th Floor, New York, NY 10010, attn: Customer Service or by email to customercare@rebeccaminkoff.com. This notice must be given before initiating any litigation or filing any claim against the other party.

In the event a dispute cannot be resolved by the above process, you consent that the dispute will be decided by binding arbitration on an individual basis— you waive the right for a judge or jury to determine your claims, and you may not proceed in a class, consolidated, or representative capacity. All such disputes shall be subject to the rules of New York, New York, before one arbitrator to be mutually agreed upon.

The failure of Rebecca Minkoff to exercise or enforce any right or provision of these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.
